Melissa Klein PUNK004
People's Archive, MLK Library
Melissa Klein Collection
1982-2002
People's Archive, MLK Library
Klein, Melissa
PUNK004
4 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1: Zines
  - Another Lo-fi Xtravaganza by Smith, Jen, Olympia, WA, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - April Fool's Day by Hanna, Kathleen, Olympia, WA, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Back by Nelson, Mark; Nelson, Ryan; Cynthia Connolly; Cristina Calle; Denno; Moats, Charlie; Lam Carlyle, Kim; Cinca, Shelby; Yeats, W.B.; MacDonnell, Katharine;, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Best of Dipper by Shaw, Dale, Washington, DC, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bikini Kill A Color and Activity Book by Bikini Kill, Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Brickthrower #2 by Brickthrower; The Stigmatics, Washington, DC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brickthrower #3 by Brickthrower, Washington, DC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fantastic Fanzine #6 by Erika Maria, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Flamer! by Flamer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Flamer! by Flamer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Girl Germs The Glory on Highway 69 by Girl Germs, Olympia, Wa, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hello Friends: Quail Season #2 by The Quails, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hello Friends: Quail Season #3 by The Quails, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hello Friends: Quail Season #5 by The Quails, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - If This Goes On #3 by If This Goes On, Bethesda, MD, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Interrobang by Cheslow, Sharon, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jigsaw #3 by Jigsaw Fanzine, Olympia, Wa, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Lady Luck by Thompson, Kim, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Most Beautiful Girl Is A Dead girl by Fingers, Maggie, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Quails Tour Diary by Julianna Bright, San Francisco, CA, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Quit Whining #1 by Margaret, Bethesda, MD; S. Hadley, MA, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Red Rover #1 by Smith, Jen, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Red Rover #2 by Smith, Jen, Washington, DC, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Red Rover #4 by Smith, Jen, Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Riot Grrrl #3 by Neuman, Molly, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Riot Grrrl #5 by Neuman, Molly, Arlington, VA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Riot Grrrl #6 by Neuman, Molly, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Riot Grrrl #1 by Neuman, Molly, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Riot Grrrl! New England #1 by Rooks, Margaret; Allie, South Hadley, MA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Riot Grrrl! A Valley Girl Production #2 by Wilson, Jessica; Allie; Rooks, Margaret; Smith, Sara; Magruder, Jenna; Gallahorn, Jen; Katsikas, Colette, Northampton, MA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Riot Grrrl A Benefit for DC's Battered Women's Shelters by Sherry; Kris; Debbie; Susan, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Serious Headgear by Charmiec, Pete, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Soul Notes 1: heroes..., past. by Thomas, N., Seattle, WA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Teen Fag #3 by Chow Chow Productions, Seattle, WA, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Teen Fag #4 by Chow Chow Productions, Seattle, WA, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Teen Fag #5 by Chow Chow Productions, Seattle, WA, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Turn Around Issue II by Thomas, Jenn; Seltzer, Dave, Silver Spring, MD, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Untitled [Hi, this is me, Becky] by Becky, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Vigil No. 2 by Zipp, Sandy, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Series 2: Printed Materials
  - Fliers, Record insert, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Series 3: Records
  - Autoclave by Autoclave, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Label: Dischord Records / Mira Records
  - King Face by King Face, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Label: self-released
  - Fugazi by Fugazi, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Label: Dischord Records
  - Rites of Spring by Rites of Spring, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Flex Your Head by Various Artists, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Post-Humorous Relief by Vile Cherubs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Label: Dischord Records / Cherubic Delusions
  - Repeater by Fugazi, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Madhouse by Madhouse, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Label: Fountain of Youth Records
  - Less Deep Inside Keeps by Soulside, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Label: Dischord Records / Sammich Records
  - Subject to Change by Faith, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minor Threat by Minor Threat, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)